https://www.jhwebworks.com/privacy-notice/

HomeWebsite DesignStart Your New WebsiteWordPress Content ManagementE-Commerce Website DevelopmentosCommerce E-Commerce SystemWooCommerce Online StoreWeb Database ApplicationsAdditional ServicesSEO ServicesDigital MarketingWebsite Hosting, Email, Domain Name RegistrationWebsite PortfolioWordPress WebsitesWooCommerce WebsitesCustom WebsitesNon-Profit WebsitesosCommerce WebsitesContent Management WebsitesSimple Ecommerce WebsitesMaintenance and UpdatesWhy Hire jhWebWorksTestimonialsWebsite or Web Designer Problems?Website Design PricingWebsite FAQsContactThis Privacy Policy governs the manner in which jhWebWorks LLC collect, use, maintain and disclose information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the jhWebWorks.com  website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by jhWebWorks LLC .Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information,Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.How we use collected informationjhWebWorks LLC  collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:To improve customer service Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.To process transactions We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.To send periodic emails The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.How we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.CookiesLike most interactive web sites this Company’s website [or ISP] uses cookies to enable us to retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are used in some areas of our site to enable the functionality of this area and ease of use for those people visiting. Some of our affiliate partners may also use cookies. [If you do not use cookies, delete this clause] Links from this websiteWe do not monitor or review the content of other party’s websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or material appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. This Company will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.Copyright NoticeCopyright and other relevant intellectual property rights exists on all text relating to the Company’s products or services and the full content of this website.The Company’s logo is a registered trademark of the Company in the USA and other countries. The brand names and specific services of the Company featured on this web site are trade marked.Client ResourcesConfigure EmailPay with PayPalPrivacy NoticeSitemapWe take online payments:      Serving Central Ohio & these communities:Columbus OhioBexley OhioCanal Winchester OhioChillicothe OhioDelaware OhioDublin OhioGahanna OhioGrandview OhioGrove City OhioGroveport OhioHilliard OhioLondon OhioNew Albany OhioPataskala OhioPickerington OhioPlain City OhioPowell OhioUpper Arlington OhioWesterville OhioWorthington OhiojhWebWorks, LLC 2800 Lake Hollow Rd Hilliard, Ohio 43026 614-777-0559 Email UsFacebookGoogle+LinkedInTwitter
